The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Knight of the Ribbon,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Thirty-Fourth Episode
The Madness of Alce
All our Kings of the past
were strong and courageous!
And all were capable
of performing exceptional feats!
Look! Look at these Kings,
how brave they were!
How beautiful and courageous
were the Kings of the past!
Certainly! I told you,
they were the bravest in the world.
Look at how strong this one was!
- And that one there? - He caught
that big whale all by himself!
Bravo! Bravo!
The Kings of old fought
against dragons with only a sword!
And when the Kings of ancient times
fought against a lion,
they carried only a
single tiny spear!
As you can see, the Kings of old
were strong and very courageous.
- And what is Prince Sapphire like?
- Well...
Well... He... Actually...
Tell me, Nylon!
Sapphire will be our next King,
won't he?
Is he also strong and courageous?
No, no, not at all! Sapphire is
neither strong nor courageous!
- Why?
- Because he has never performed...
...an achievement so important
that it can be displayed in here.
So he is not as good as he seems!
No, Princess Sapphire,
please stay calm!
If you get angry, it will
be trouble for everyone!
It's better if you go over
there, I'll keep an eye on them!
He seems strong!
But in reality, he is weak!
Hurray!
Sapphire is not strong at all!
Sapphire is weak!
- Weak Sapphire has arrived!
- What?!
Nylon said that you are
not as brave as you seem.
What are you saying?
Welcome, Princess Sapphire
and Doctor Uranaru.
Nylon, why do you say that I am not
as brave as I seem?
Well, I only said...
...that you haven't had a chance
to prove your courage.
Nylon! I will never forgive you
if you say unkind things...
...about
Princess Sapphire!
So, Princess Sapphire,
why don't you try to prove...
...your courage to Plastic?
- Prove my courage?!
There is a deer named Alce who lives
in the forest near the castle.
He is no ordinary deer; he is huge!
Not only that! When hunters
go looking for animals,
he suddenly appears
and attacks them!
He always wins and then leaves!
It is said that now
everyone is afraid of him...
...and they stay away from the forest.
So, do you want to defeat
the great deer?
I didn't know there was
such a deer in the forest! All right, I'll do it!
Opal, come here!
Run to the forest immediately!
- Sapphire! Where are you going?
- Hi, Tink, I was looking for you
Is that the forest
where a deer named Alce lives?
Alce...?
Yes, this is it!
- Opale, let's go!
- Sapphire, wait! No!
I wonder why Sapphire
is going to that place. It's dangerous!
If Alce attacks him
he will hurt him!
It's very dark in the forest! Opale,
stay here, I'll look for him by myself!
Hey, hello! Do you know Alce?
Hey, do you know Alce?
But it's strange! Why is
everyone running away?
Don't hurt me, please!
Help! Help!
Now I'll teach you to laugh!
Wait! Wait!
Go!
Don't do it anymore!
You are Alce, right? Because of you, no
one can come into the woods anymore!
I have come to defeat you!
Where did he go? I don't
want him to get away!
How big you are!
Princess Sapphire might be in danger!
I'm worried!
Here she comes back!
Princess Sapphire, did
you encounter the deer?
Yes! And he knocked me to the ground
with a blow from his horns!
Well, I'm sorry,
Princess Sapphire.
Not even you can defeat him!
But if I had been there...
You wouldn't have been able to do
anything at all,
because Moose's head alone
is this big!
What?! His head is this big?!
So, Prince Sapphire,
did you manage to kill Moose?
He's still alive in the woods. I'm letting him
live for a few more days.
Ah, I see! It's not that by any chance
you're a little afraid of him, right?
- Me, afraid?!
- I mean... what I mean is.
If you don't manage to kill him
what will you do?
I will defeat him
without using my sword!
But when I've defeated him
what will you do?
Well, I'll stand on top of the tower
like a flag! Like this! Look!
Very interesting!
In the meantime, start practicing.
Princess Sapphire, let's go,
you must rest!
Are you sure you did the right thing
by promising him such a thing?
Sapphire might even be
capable of defeating Alce!
Don't worry!
- I have a way to avoid it!
- What is it?
Be careful! If you touch
the tip you will go mad!
It will be enough just
to hit him anywhere...
..with this poisonous arrow
that the natives of Africa use!
Let me handle everything!
- I can't take it anymore!
- Princess Sapphire, are you alright?
The sun is almost high,
it would be time to stop!
One more time!
But I'm sorry to throw
you to the ground again!
One more time!
- Oh, no!
- Is everything alright, Princess?
The way things are going, I understand.
.. ...that I cannot defeat
Alce, at least not with a sword!
Send out more and more smoke!
- We are ready, Mr. Nylon.
- Alright, begin!
But what are you doing?
Don't stop!
Hurry and send the smoke
into the woods!
We need to drive the animals
out, do you understand?
Soon that cursed Alce
will appear! Are you ready?
Kill him..! Surround him...
Don't let him escape..!
But this is truly a monster!
But no monster
could climb up this far!
When he is hit by the
arrow, he will go mad!
And now, go as wild
as you like!
Now I really want to see
how Sapphire will catch him!
If he should meet him, furious
as he is, he will tear him to pieces!
Here comes Alce!
Hello, Alce, where are
you going in such a hurry?
Watch out for the sheep!
My God!
What is this shiny thing?
What happened to Alce?
He seems to have gone mad!
Alce is running wild
through the whole city...
...and the soldiers
cannot stop him!
So we would like you to come
and try, Princess Sapphire!
Just in time! I have just finished
devising a way to kill him!
If Alce has two horns, well...
I will have three swords!
But not three hands!
Fine! Do you perhaps intend
to throw the swords at him?
Don't worry, my idea
will work! Let's go, Opal!
Good luck!
Yeah, she'll need a lot of it!
He's arrived,
but he's destroying the city
Come, Alce!
This time I'll get you!
Sapphire!
Don't kill him!
Remove the arrow he has on his neck!
Arrow?! I think Tink
said to pull out an arrow!
Ah, there it is!
Sapphire!
Hurry and bring some ropes!
Bring more!
Hey, you!
Quickly, tie the other end
to the tree!
Sapphire!
Sapphire, hold on tight!
Come on, Alce, open your eyes!
Sapphire has removed the arrow!
Now it's all over!
Listen, Moose..
A bad man shot
a poisoned arrow at you,
but she helped you.
She is telling you to forgive him.
I am the one who must apologize to you...
...because I intended
to kill you.
Hurray! Hurray!
Did you see? He captured Moose!
Now you will have to keep your promise!
Oh, no! I am sure I shot
the arrow hitting him in the neck!
Quick, you idiot!
Go be the flag..
...on top of that tower!
- Let me try again!
I have another arrow! If I shoot it
at Alce, Sapphire will fall and die!
Hurray!
Princess!
Nylon!
Watch out!
No! Wait!
Wait, I didn't want to hit you!
Help!
Help! Help! Wait!
It's just as I thought.
Sapphire is not weak at all!
You're right! He will be
a strong and brave King!
Princess Sapphire, will Alce have
returned safe and sound to the forest?
That's exactly what I was thinking.
And now, Alce..
Take care of yourself!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP